Bees Tak brings you a premium
membership program where you will get many
benefits like gym, market newsletter, live
chat, first answers to your questions on Maa's
Doubt Look Way Can, market scan,
chat with anchors and much more. This
premium subscription has three types of
plans - Silver, Gold and Platinum,
starting from 105 per month.
Joining is also very easy.
Click on the Join button on Mr.'s YouTube channel
and select your plan.
You have become our premium member.
Today, there was a bullish atmosphere in the Indian market.
Bank Nifty made a new high today.
Nifty Bank reached a new high today after December 14, 2022
and it
went to 44350 for the first time. But
banking stocks had a huge contribution in this rally. Today,
a stock came on our radar which
rose by 14 percent after a news came. Now let's
try to understand this entire news in detail.
In April, ICC Bank sold its stake
in its insurance company i.e. ICC
Lombard General Insurance.
ICC Bank sold its stake in its
insurance company i.e. ICC Lombard
General Insurance.  The
company's board of directors also approved
increasing its stake in ICC Lombard General Insurance.
As soon as the company received approval from the board, the
bank informed the exchange about this.
Now understand the share figures.
Currently, the bank holds
2.5% of its 48.00% stake in ICC Lombard before 9 September 2014.
After this news, a
storm was seen in the market of ICC Lombard General Insurance.
In the initial trade itself, the
share of ICC Lombard General Insurance
rose by 14%. The report of the domestic broker house
also came after this news.
According to Motilal Oswal, the share
can rise by another 10 to 15% from the current level. Let us tell you that
Motilal Oswal has
advised to buy the share of ICC Lombard General Insurance.
According to this, the share can reach the level of 1400
in the coming time. Let us tell you that the
share of ICC Lombard General Insurance is currently
trading around 1200. In a month,
this share has made Nipeshwar  It has given a return of 10%, whereas
in one year it has sunk the money of Nirvaas
by 7.31%.
But if you look at the 5-year charts of this lion,
you will find that this lion has
also given a strong return of 65.41% to Nirvaas.
Now before leaving, let us find out which other banks were given permission by the central bank of the country i.e.
RBI to increase their
stake in their insurance companies.
In the month of March this year, Reserve Bank of
India had given more time to ICC Bank to
increase its stake in the insurance company.
Before ICC Bank, Reserve Bank had
also
given permission to HDFC Bank to increase its stake in its insurance subsidiary company. At that
time, Reserve Bank had given permission
to HDFC Bank to increase its stake by more than 50% in its insurance subsidiary company i.e.
HDFC Life Insurance and HDFC Ego
General Insurance.
[Music]